Read family papers LCP.Read
Library Company of Philadelphia
- Series V. Judge John M. Read II
  - Business papers, The United States vs. Colonel Charles H. T. Collis, 1863 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence from Charles Sumner, 1864 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence from Michael Meyfert, Harry Conrad, Willard Hall, Charles Caldwell, Stephen Holbrook, and others, 1864 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence from Michael Meyfert, Harry Conrad, Willard Hall, Charles Caldwell, Stephen Holbrook, and others, 1864 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence from family members including Amelia Thomson, William H. Hyde, Phineas J. Horowitz, Samuel R. Meredith, Emma H. Hyde, Charlotte M. Holbrooke, and others, 1864 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, incoming and outgoing, to John Meredith Read Jr., 1864 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, incoming and outgoing, to John Meredith Read Jr., 1864 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence from Charles H. T. Collis, Septima Sevy Collis, and William H. French, 1864 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, business (agreements between Samuel G. Hathaway and others from 1857), 1864-1865 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, personal and family, 1864-1865 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, personal and family, 1864-1865 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Business papers and correspondence, 1864-1880 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, business and invitations, 1865 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, family and personal (mostly John Meredith Read, Charles H. T. Collis, and Dr. Phineas Horowitz), 1865 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, personal and family, 1865 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Business papers, correspondence, notes, pamphlets, 1865 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence from John W. Duncan, John Meredith Read Jr., Delphine Marie Pumpelly, William H. Hyde, George W. Biddle, Harry Conrad, and others (some newspaper clippings9, 1866 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence from John Meredith Read Jr., William H. Hyde, Phineas J. Horowitz, Charles Francis Adams, Charles H. T. Collis, and others, 1866 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence from William H. Hyde, William B. Clymer, Phineas Horowitz, John Meredith Read Jr., Emma H. Hyde, Charles H. T. Collis, and others, 1866 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence from William H. Hyde, Emma H. Hyde, John Meredith Read Jr., Harmon Pumpelly Read, Charles H. T. Collis, and others, 1866 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, personal and family (mostly Catherine M. Thomson, Charles H. T. Collis, and John Meredith Read Jr.), 1865 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, personal and family (mostly Catherine M. Thomson, Charles H. T. Collis, and John Meredith Read Jr.), 1865 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Business papers, correspondence, financial notes, legal notes, 1865 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, business and personal, 1866-1869 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, business and personal, 1866 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, family, 1866 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence from Phineas Horowitz, James T. Mitchell, William H. Hyde, Charles H. T. Collis, John Meredith Read Jr., Harmon Pumpelly Read, Emily Read, and others, 1867 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence from Edward M. Clymer, John Meredith Read Jr., Carrie M. Thomson, Charles H. T. Collis, Emma H. Hyde, W. H. Rawle, John L. Cadwalader, and others, 1867 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence from John Meredith Read Jr., Charles H. T. Collis, Emma H. Hyde, William H. Hyde, Phineas Horowitz, Carrie M. Thomson, and others, 1867 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Business papers, legal documents, 1868, 1870 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, business and personal, 1868 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, business and personal, 1869 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Business papers, financial papers, legal papers, 1870 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence from James Rob Snowden, 1872 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, to Judge John Meredith Read Jr. from General John Meredith Read, 1873 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, incoming and outgoing, to John Meredith Read Jr., 1874 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Estate of the Honorable John M. Read, account of executer William Henry Rawle, 1876 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1880s (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Papers associated with Judge John Meredith's death, correspondence with Michael Meylert and William Henry Rawle), 1881-1882 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Business papers, correspondence, undated (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Business papers, correspondence, undated (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Business papers, correspondence, undated (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Business papers, correspondence, undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Business papers, correspondence, undated (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Series VI. General John Meredith Read Jr.
  - Subseries I. Address books, notebooks, memoranda books
    - Address books, notebooks, memoranda books, number 1-8, Paris, circa 1879-1896 (Box 57, Folder 1-8)
  - Subseries II. Archives du General Meredith Read
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1869 (Volume 1)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1870 (Volume 2)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1871 (Volume 3)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1872 January 1-April 31 (Volume 4)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1872 May 1-August 31 (Volume 5)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1872 September 1-December 31 (Volume 6)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1873 January-March (Volume 7)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1873 April-June (Volume 8)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1873 July-September (Volume 9)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1873 October-December (Volume 10)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1874 (Volume 11)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1875 January-June (Volume 12)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1875 July 1-1875 December 31 (Volume 13)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1876 January-April (Volume 14)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1876 May-August (Volume 15)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1876 September-December (Volume 16)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1877 January-April (Volume 17)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1877 May-August (Volume 18)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1877 September-December (Volume 19)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1878 January 1-March 13 (Volume 20)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1878 March 13-December 31 (Volume 21)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1879 (Volume 22)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1887 (Volume 23)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1888 (Volume 24)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1890-1891 (Volume 25)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1891-1892 (Volume 26)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1893 (Volume 27)
    - Henry Hudson research and papers, 1869, 1894 (Volume 28)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1894-1895 (Volume 29)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, invitations, visiting cards, and other papers, 1895-1896 (Volume 30)
    - Invitations received, 1886-1890 (Volume 31)
    - Invitations received, 1890-1892 (Volume 32)
    - Invitations received, 1893-1894 (Volume 33)
    - Invitations received, 1894-1896 (Volume 34)
    - Invitations sent and answers received, 1889 (Volume 35)
    - Invitations sent and answers received, 1890-1893 (Volume 36)
    - Invitations sent and answers received, 1893-1896 (Volume 37)
    - [Distinguished correspondence?], 1867-1884 (Volume 38)
    - [Distinguished correspondence?], 1885-1889 (Volume 39)
    - Distinguished people papers, 1889-1894 (Volume 40)
    - Distinguished people papers, 1894-1896 (Volume 41)
    - Correspondence, social, 1889 (Volume 42)
    - Lord Amherst Centennial of the Town of Barry, 1868 (Volume 43)
    - Athlumney Meredith, 1873-1883 (Volume 44)
    - Barton Beedon, Brocket Dunstew, Reading Chirk Castle, 1886-1894 (Volume 45)
    - Sir Bernard Burke and His Family, 1872-1897 (Volume 46)
    - Cadwalader, 1889-1896 (Volume 47)
    - Mr. Coote and the British Museum, 1888-1895 (Volume 48)
    - Davis, C., Judic Agnew, and the Howell Family, 1889-1895 (Volume 49)
    - Lord Devon, Viscount Halifax, Duke of St. Albans, Earl of St. Germans, 1873-1895 (Volume 50)
    - Mr. Heron, 1893-1896 (Volume 51)
    - Lord Lytton, 1873-1892 (Volume 52)
    - Marshall and Waterman Families, 1887-1897 (Volume 53)
    - Meredith Family of America, 1890-1896 (Volume 54)
    - Mr. Parker, 1888-1890 (Volume 55)
    - Mr. Parker, 1888-1893 (Volume 56)
    - Mr. Parker, 1893-1895 (Volume 57)
    - Pumpelly, 1841-1886 (Volume 58)
    - Read family, American Branch, 1894-1896 (Volume 59)
    - Read family, American Branch, 1891-1894 (Volume 60)
    - The Reads, Philadelphia, Albany, Delaware, and Arkansas, 1870-1890 (Volume 61)
    - Arthur E. Reade, Esq., and his Father, Edward A. Reade, Esq., 1859-1886 (Volume 62)
    - Charles Reade, D. C. L., 1875 (Volume 63)
    - Compton Reade, Esq. and Reverend Compton Reade, 1883-1893 (Volume 64)
    - Family of General Meredith Read, 1893-1896 (Volume 65)
    - The Meredith Read Ffamily of Portugal and the Marquis de Thomar, 1878-1879 (Volume 66)
    - Read/Reade Pedigree, 1886-1906 (Volume 67)
    - Ross, 1889-1895 (Volume 68)
    - Shipton, 1886-1895 (Volume 69)
    - Lord Salisbury, Lorde Stanhope, Comte de Remersat, 1876-1891 (Volume 70)
    - Mr. B. J. Stevens, 1890-1896 (Volume 71)
    - Lord Talbot de Malahide, 1871-1873 (Volume 72)
    - Wynn family, 1870-1890 (Volume 73)
    - Clubs and Societies, 1890-1895 (Volume 74)
    - Passports and personal papers, 1871-1879 (Volume 75)
    - Diner des Spartiates, 1888-1891 (Volume 76)
    - Société des Bibliophiles Contemporains (Volume 77)
  - Subseries III. Business Papers
    - Business papers, financial papers, legal papers, 1849-1850 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Visiting cards, circa 1850 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Poole's Gentleman's Pocket Memorandum Book, 1857 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Court Cases, 1859-1860 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Notebooks with annotations (business and personal), circa 1860 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Legal notes, undated (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Blank notebook, undated (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Court Cases: Harmon Pumpelly vs. L. M. Chase, circa 1862 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Cornell University: establishment act, first general announcement, and related correspondence and newspaper clippings, 1865-1868 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Business papers, correspondence, leases, invitations, newspaper clippings, 1871-1895 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Notebooks, personal and business, circa 1879 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Notebooks, personal and business: "Addresses-Greece under King George" and "Addresses", 1879 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Business papers, notes, receipt book, 1880-1889 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Subseries IV. Correspondence
    - Correspondence form Delphine Drake Pumpelly about her death and illness, circa 1839 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (mostly with Emily Marshall Read) and pictures of Besselsleigh, England and a well at Isden, 1841-1843, 1883 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence from family in Providence, Rhode Island, 1842 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Pumpelly family letters (Mostly to Delphine M. Pumpelly), 1848-1850 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (Mostly with Adeline Pumpelly and Delphine Pumpelly), 1834-1854 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence relating to the Young Men's Association of Albany, New York, 1854-1867 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence with John Meredith Read, notes, Brown University papers, and newspaper clippings, 1855-1860 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence from European trip to John Meredith Read and Aunt, 1857 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence from European trip to John Meredith Read and Aunt, 1858 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence and European trip notes and miscellaneous documents, 1857 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence relating to military career, 1857-1861 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, business and personal, 1859 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence from George Bancroft, William J. Read, and others, 1860 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1860-1869 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Letterpress book, 1860-1865 (Volume 94)
    - Correspondence from Charlotte Cushman, circa 1860 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence from John Meredith Read, 1861 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Letterpress book, 1861 (Volume 95)
    - Correspondence from Ricketts, 1862 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence between John Meredith Read Jr. and New York Governor E. D. Morgan, related newspaper clippings, 1863 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence from John Meredith Read Jr. concerning his address before the Historical Society of Delaware and from E. D. Morgan, 1864 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence with and notes related to Albert Bierstadt, 1864-1868 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence from E. D. Morgan, M. R. Fisher, John Meredith Read, and Reverend Leighton Coleman, 1865 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence from John Meredith Read, 1865 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence book, 1865-1869 (Volume 96)
    - Correspondence relating to book on Henry Hudson and from John Meredith Read, expense book, 1866 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence with H. W. Longfellow, C. F. Adams, G. Bancroft, Senator Morgan, E. Agassiz, S. Weir Mitchell, C. Eliot Norton, John Stay, James B. Angell, F. Parkman, Roscoe Conkling, H. J. Raymond, W. D. Howells, Goldwin Smith, and John A. Dix, 1866-1869 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence from John Meredith Read and relating to Henry Hudson book, 1867 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence from John Meredith Read, 1868 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence concerning 1868 presidential campaign (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence relating to appointment as Consul-General, 1869 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence between John Meredith Read and John Meredith Read Jr., 1869 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, business and personal, 1869 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence concerning the American Social Science Congress at Albany, New York, 1869 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence from the Paris Consulate scrapbook, 1869-1873 (Volume 97)
    - Correspondence from the Paris Consulate scrapbook, 1869-1874 (Volume 98)
    - Correspondence from the Paris Consulate letterpress book, 1869 July-1871 October (Volume 99)
    - Correspondence from the Paris Consulate letterpress book, 1869 September-1870 June (Volume 100)
    - Correspondence from the Paris Consulate letterpress book, 1869 July-1871 March (Volume 101)
    - Correspondence from the Paris Consulate letterpress book, 1869 July-1871 November (Volume 102)
    - Correspondence from the Paris Consulate letterpress book, 1869-1871 (Volume 103)
    - Correspondence relating to sieges of Paris, 1870-1871 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence from the Paris Consulate letterpress book, 1870 June 22-1873 January 30 (Volume 104)
    - Correspondence, 1870-1886 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence from the Paris Consulate letterpress book, 1871 March-1871 November (Volume 105)
    - Correspondence from the Paris Consulate letterpress book, 1871 December-1873 January (Volume 106)
    - Correspondence and newspaper clippings scrapbook ("Greek Ministry"), 1871-1886 (Volume 107)
    - Correspondence, 1871-1879 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence from the Paris Consulate letterpress book (1 of 2), 1872 September-1873 March (Volume 108)
    - Correspondence from the Paris Consulate letterpress book (2 of 2), 1873 September-March (Volume 109)
    - Correspondence from the Paris Consulate letterpress book, 1873 March-July (Volume 110)
    - Correspondence from the Paris Consulate letterpress book, 1873 July-December (Volume 111)
    - Correspondence, personal papers, newspaper clippings, 1874 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Greek Ministry letterpress book, 1874 February-June (Volume 112)
    - Correspondence, Greek Ministry letterpress book, 1874 April-June (Volume 113)
    - Correspondence, 1875 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1876 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1876-1886 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1876-1896 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and personal papers, 1876-1896 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1877 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1877 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence scrapbook from the Greek Ministry, 1877-1878 (Volume 114)
    - Correspondence, 1878 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence from King George I of Greece, 1878 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence and newspaper clippings scrapbook, 1878-1901 (Volume 115)
    - Correspondence, 1879 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence from King George I, 1879 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, book of letter copies, 1879 September-1880 April (Volume 116)
    - Correspondence from King George I of Greece, 1880 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Military button from King George I of Greece, 1880 (Box 65)
    - Book of Correspondence with Mrs. Meredith Read, London letters, 1880 (Volume 117)
    - Correspondence and visiting cards scrapbook, London letters, 1880 (Volume 118)
    - Correspondence, letterbook, Paris, 1880, 1886 (Volume 119)
    - Correspondence, letterbook, Paris, 1880-1881 (Volume 120)
    - Correspondence and receipts, 1880-1889 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1880-1893 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1880-1896 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and telegraphs between John Meredith Read Jr. and Queen Victoria's secretaries, 1880-1896 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence from Prince and Princess of Wales, Charlotte Knollys, Lord Colville, Sir Francis Knollys, and S. C. Clarke, 1880-1896 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence from Prince and Princess of Wales, Charlotte Knollys, Lord Colville, Sir Francis Knollys, and S. C. Clarke, 1880-1896 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1880-1896 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1880-1896 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence from Duke of Connaught, 1880-1896 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence from King George I of Greece, circa 1880 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, letterbook, Paris, 1881 October 16-1882 February 14 (Volume 121)
    - Correspondence, letterbook, Paris, 1882 February 15-July 21 (Volume 122)
    - Correspondence from King George I of Greece, 1882 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence from King George I of Greece, 1884 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence and receipts, 1884 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence with Martha Lamb of the Magazine of American History, 1885-1892 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence book with letters from Samuel Sartain (engraver) and Broadbent Brothers (photographers), 1885-1886 (Volume 123)
    - Correspondence from King George I of Greece, 1886 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence from King George I of Greece, 1888 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence from King George I of Greece, 1889 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence from King George I of Greece, 1890 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence scrapbook of letters concerning Robert Morris, 1890-1891 (Volume 124)
    - Correspondence concerning Mayville speculations and newspaper clippings, 1891-1894 (Volume 125)
    - Correspondence, 1891-1895 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence from King George I of Greece, 1891 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence from King George I of Greece, 1892 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence from King George I of Greece, 1893 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence about Thomas Jefferson Coolidge, Paris, 1893 (Volume 126)
    - Correspondence and newspaper clippings, American Chamber of Commerce and Paris, 1893 (Volume 127)
    - Correspondence and newspaper clippings scrapbook, Paris and the Lafayette Ceremony, undated (Volume 128)
    - Correspondence from King George I of Greece, 1894 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence from King George I of Greece, 1895 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence from King George I of Greece, 1896 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Subseries V. Genealogy
    - The Ross family genealogical research conducted by General John Meredith Read, 1872-1874 (Volume 129)
    - Portraits and Illustrations relating to genealogical research, circa 1876 (Volume 130)
    - Correspondence from Major Harmon Read to General John Meredith Read regarding Ross and Read families, 1882 August (Volume 131)
    - Correspondence to General John Meredith Read about family history, 1882-1886 (Volume 132)
    - Genealogical and historical scrapbook about Captain Thomas Read, 1883-1885 (Volume 133)
    - Cadwalader and Howell families, genealogical correspondence, 1883-1886 (Volume 134)
    - Genealogical research scrapbook on Thomas Read by General John Meredith Read, 1885 (Volume 135)
    - Delaware Society of the Cincinnati scrapbook, 1895-1909 (Volume 136)
    - Notebook with genealogy notes, undated (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Cemetery and memorial transcriptions book, undated (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Pedigree of Read family, undated (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Subseries VI. Newspaper Clippings and Publications
    - Newspaper clippings scrapbook, 1859-1863 (Volume 137)
    - Albany Journal, New York Times, New York Tribune, 1863-1868 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper clippings in English and Greek; "Postal Treaty between France and Greece", 1867-1879 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper clippings scrapbook, Paris Consulate, 1870 (Volume 138)
    - Newspaper clippings scrapbook, Paris Consulate (miscellaneous English clippings), 1871-1874 (Volume 139)
    - Newspaper clippings scrapbook, Greek Ministry, 1873-1874 (Volume 140)
    - Collected publications, pamphlets, and newspaper articles, 1873-1889 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper clippings scrapbook, Greek Ministry, extracts from Greek newspapers with translations, 1874 (Volume 141)
    - Calignani's Messenger, 1874 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper clippings and collected articles and writings, 1876-1896 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper clippings scrapbook, 1879-1896 (Volume 142)
    - New York Herald, Morris Chronicle, and others, 1883-1895 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper clippings and correspondence, 1887-1889 (Volume 143)
    - Newspaper clippings scrapbook, 1893-1894 (Volume 144)
  - Subseries VII. Palaeographia
    - Palaeographia of correspondence, 1869 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Palaeographia of correspondence, 1870 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Palaeographia of correspondence, 1871 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Palaeographia of correspondence, 1872 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Palaeographia of correspondence, journal, 1873 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Subseries VIII. Photographs